

OKSANA VLASENKO

Senior Frontend Developer

+:

+38(063)-582-9166



vlasenkoksenia642@gmail.com



@kseniaVlasenko



https://oksanavlasenko.github.io/vlasenko

EDUCATION

Master degree of CyberSecurity

V. N. Karazin Kharkiv National University

2013 - 2019

CERTIFICATIONS

Official EF SET Certificate | Oksana Vlasenko | C2 (72/100)

GITHUB

LINKEDIN

SKILLS

- Vue 2, 3
- VUEX
- Tailwind CSS
- Vue Router
- Solid.js
- React
- JavaScript
- HTML / CSS
- SCSS
- i18n

HOBBIES

- Dancing
- Reading
- Pilates

LANGUAGE

- Ukrainian Native
- English Advanced

PROFILE

I'm a software developer with 4+ years of web development. I'm proficient in JavaScript, Vue 2, Vue 3, React.js, Node.js, Express,js, Solid.js, Tailwind CSS, TypeScript etc. My goal is delivering the best possible user experience, performance, and intuitiveness in the products I develop.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FixIQ Pro

2021.09-2024.07 (2y 11m)

- Develop new features, maintain codebase, perform code reviews, increase perfomance though refactor
- Part of a team creating a micro front end using Solid.js.
- Mentor junior developers
- Make intergations with Checkbox, Quickbooks, Sendpulse
- Technologies: Vue 2, Vuex, Vue Router, Solid.js, Vue 3, Tailwind CSS, il8n

Medstar Solutions

2021.06 - 2021.09 (4m)

- Worked on a Vue 2 application.
- Created new components, maintained features, and wrote unit tests with Jest.

Self employed

2020.04 - 2021.05 (1y 2m)

 Worked with the MERN stack, Vue 2, React, and native JavaScript.

Varion

2020.01 - 2020.04 (4 m)

- Developed games with Phaser.js
- Developed new features with Vue 2 and native JavaScript

REFERENCES

Roman Almazov

Lead Frontend Engineer

Edison Donets Lead QA Engineer

Telegram: @ralmaz

Telegram: @edison_edison05